Guide to the Johan Kugelberg hip hop collection, circa 1975-1985, 2008.
Kugelberg, Johan hip hop collection,
- Series I. Sound Recordings (1-24)
  - LPs - SR 776-827 (Box 16)
    - Horse ride / the Mark IV Performed by: Mark IV, 1980; SR-824 (Box 16)
      Publisher: Tree Line
      Track listing: Horse ride (long version) -- Horse ride (short version).
    - Sexy freek / Mario Performed by: Mario, 1984; SR-825 (Box 16)
      Track listing: Sexy freek (street version) -- Sexy freek (street scratch version).
    - Boogie down (Bronx) Performed by: Man Parrish; featuring Freeze Force, 1984; SR-826 (Box 16)
      Track listing: Boogie down (Bronx) -- Boogie down (dub).
    - Man Parrish Performed by: Man Parrish; with vocal and instrumental acc, 1982; SR-827 (Box 16)
      Publisher: Importe/12
      Track listing: Hip hop, be bop (don't stop) -- In the beginning -- Man made -- Together again -- Hip hop, be bop (part 2) -- Six simple synthesizers -- Techno trax -- Street clap -- Heatstroke.
  - LPs - SR 828-851 (Box 17)
    - Duck rock / Malcolm McLaren Performed by: Kurtis Blow (Malcolm McLaren), 1983; SR-828 (Box 17)
      Publisher: Charisma
      Track listing: Obatala -- Buffalo gals -- Double dutch -- Merengue -- Punk it up -- Legba -- Jive my baby -- Song for Chango -- Soweto -- World's famous -- Duck for the oyster.
    - Duck rock / Malcolm McLaren Performed by: Malcolm McLaren, 1983; SR-829 (Box 17)
    - Kurtis Blow Performed by: Malcolm McLaren, 1980; SR-830 (Box 17)
      Track listing: Rappin' Blow (part 2) -- The breaks -- Way out west -- Throughout your years -- Hard times -- All I want in this world (is to find that girl) -- Takin' care of business.
    - Rappin' Blow / Kurtis Blow Performed by: Kurtis Blow, 1979; SR-831 (Box 17)
      Track listing: Rappin' Blow -- Rappin' Blow (do it yourself version-instrumental).
    - 8 million stories; AJ scratch / Kurtis Blow Performed by: Kurtis Blow, 1984; SR-832 (Box 17)
      Track listing: 8 million stories -- AJ scratch.
    - Rapture rapp / Liberty Silver Performed by: Liberty Silver, ca. 1985; SR-833 (Box 17)
      Track listing: Rapture rapp -- Rapture rapp (instrumental).
    - Word up Performed by: Legacy, 1982; SR-834 (Box 17)
      Publisher: Brunswick
      Track listing: Word up (6:45) -- Word up (Instrumental) (6:03).
    - Rockin-poppin full tilting / Lee Alfred Performed by: Lee Alfred, 1980; SR-835 (Box 17)
      Publisher: Cancer Records
      Track listing: Rockin-poppin full tilting -- Rockin-poppin full tilting.
    - Do the right thing; Starski live at the Fever / "Love Bug" Starski Performed by: "Love Bug" Starski, 1984; SR-836 (Box 17)
      Publisher: Fever
      Track listing: Do the right thing (vocal) -- Do the right thing (instrumental) -- Starski live at the Fever pt. II (vocal) -- Starski live at the Fever pt. II (instrumental).
    - You've gotta believe; Starski live at the Disco Fever / "Love Bug" Starski Performed by: "Love Bug" Starski, ca. 1985; SR-837 (Box 17)
      Track listing: You've gotta believe (vocal) -- Starski live at the Disco Fever (vocal) -- You've gotta believe (instrumental) -- Starski live at the Disco Fever (instrumental).
    - Video burnout / Little Toni Marsh Performed by: Little Toni Marsh, ca. 1985; SR-838 (Box 17)
      Track listing: Video burnout -- Video burnout (dub version).
    - Lisa; Skateboard / the Little Rapscals Performed by: Little Rapscals, ca. 1980; SR-839 (Box 17)
      Publisher: PEP Records
      Track listing: Lisa (vocal) -- Lisa (dub) -- Skateboard.
    - Christmas rappin' Performed by: Kurtis Blow, 1979; SR-840 (Box 17)
      Track listing: Christmas rappin' -- Christmas rappin' (do it yourself version-instrumental).
    - Breaks; Rappin'; Tough / Kurtis Blow Performed by: Kurtis Blow, 1980; SR-841 (Box 17)
      Track listing: The breaks -- Rappin' -- Tough.
    - Breaks / Kurtis Blow Performed by: Kurtis Blow, 1980; SR-842 (Box 17)
      Track listing: The breaks (vocal) -- The breaks (instrumental).
    - It's rockin time (rock rockin time) / Kool Kyle (the Starchild); music by Pumpkin & Friends Performed by: Kool Kyle (the Starchild); music by Pumpkin & Friends, 1981; SR-843 (Box 17)
      Track listing: It's rockin time (rock rockin time) (vocal) -- It's rockin time (rock rockin time) (instrumental).
    - Getting over / Kool Kyle (the original Star Child) Performed by: Kool Kyle, 1982; SR-844 (Box 17)
      Track listing: Getting over -- Getting over (instrumental).
    - Video Jones / Komputer Kid with Gripp Band Performed by: Komputer Kid with Gripp Band, 1983; SR-845 (Box 17)
      Publisher: Jones Records
      Track listing: Video Jones (vocal) -- Video Jones (instrumental).
    - Charley says! Performed by: King Tim III, vocals; with instrumental acc, 1980; SR-846 (Box 17)
      Track listing: Charley says! (roller boogie baby) (vocal) -- Charley says! (roller boogie baby) (instrumental).
    - Nairobi and the Awesome Foursome Performed by: Nairobi and the Awesome Foursome, vocal and instrumental ensembles, 1982; SR-847 (Box 17)
      Track listing: Funky soul Makossa (rap) -- Free beats -- Funky soul Makossa -- Makossa jam (instrumental).
    - Jam on it Performed by: Newcleus, 1984; SR-848 (Box 17)
      Track listing: Jam on it -- Jam on it (instrumental).
    - On the dance floor / New Guys on the Block, featuring Lane Performed by: New Guys on the Block, 1983; SR-849 (Box 17)
      Publisher: Polarvox
      Track listing: On the dance floor (vocal) -- On the dance floor (instrumental).
    - Electric boogaloo / Ollie & Jerry Performed by: Ollie & Jerry; remixed by John "Jellybean" Benitez, 1984; SR-850 (Box 17)
      Track listing: Electric boogaloo (dance mix) -- Electric boogaloo (instrumental).
    - Breakin' -- there's no stopping us / Ollie and Jerry Performed by: Ollie and Jerry; remixed by John "Jellybean" Benitez, 1984; SR-851 (Box 17)
      Track listing: Breakin'-- there's no stopping us (club mix) -- Breakin'-- there's no stopping us (instrumental).
  - LPs - Duplicates of some items from Box 1-17 (Box 18)
    - Live convention "81" / various artists Performed by: Wheels of Steel, Cut Creators, Cheif's [sic] Rockers, and others, 1981; SR-23 c.2 (Box 18)
    - All the way: Live in '82 / Cold Crush Brothers Performed by: Cold Crush Brothers, 1994; SR-24 c.2 (Box 18)
    - Joseph Papp presents Runaways / written, composed, and directed by Elizabeth Swados Performed by: Elizabeth Swados, 1978; SR-38 c.2 (Box 18)
    - Joseph Papp presents Runaways / written, composed, and directed by Elizabeth Swados Performed by: Elizabeth Swados, 1978; SR-38 c.3 (Box 18)
    - UN rap song; Dance to your TV Performed by: Stew Lane and the Untouchables, 1980; SR-43 c.2 (Box 18)
    - Roller dancing for fun & fitness Performed by: [Unknown], 1980; SR-47 c.2 (Box 18)
    - Breakdance Performed by: Various performers, 1984; SR-65 c.2 (Box 18)
    - Trash talkin' / Albert Collins Performed by: Albert Collins, vocals & guitar with instrumental ensemble, 1969; SR-77 c.2 (Box 18)
    - Love money / Funk Masters (Money) no love / Bo Kool Performed by: Funk Masters, 1981; SR-91 c.2 (Box 18)
    - Big apple rappin': (National rappin' anthem) / Spyder-D Performed by: Spyder-D, 1980; SR-121 c.2 (Box 18)
    - Born in the Bronx!: a visual record of rap's early days Performed by: Various performers, 2005; SR-129 c.2 (Box 18)
    - Born in the Bronx!: a visual record of rap's early days Performed by: Various performers, 2005; SR-129 c.3 (Box 18)
    - Born in the Bronx!: a visual record of rap's early days Performed by: Various performers, 2005; SR-129 c.4 (Box 18)
    - Born in the Bronx!: a visual record of rap's early days Performed by: Various performers, 2005; SR-129 c.5 (Box 18)
    - Rhymin' and rappin'; Watch dog Performed by: Various performers, 1979; SR-159 c.2 (Box 18)
    - Make it, shake it, do it good / Parlez (Par-lay) Performed by: Parlez, ca. 1985; SR-173 c.2 (Box 18)
    - Jazzy sensation Performed by: Afrika Bambaataa, vocals; Jazzy 5, instrumental ensemble; Kryptic Krew, instrumental ensemble, featuring Tina B, ca.1985; SR-185 c.2 (Box 18)
    - Megamix II: why is it fresh? / D St Performed by: D. St, 1984; SR-189 c.2 (Box 18)
    - Take my rap please / Steve Gordon & The Kosher Five Performed by: Steve Gordon, 1979; SR-234 c.2 (Box 18)
    - Ladies delight Performed by: Mr. Q, ca.1975; SR-287 c.2 (Box 18)
    - Rapper's delight / Sugar Hill Gang Performed by: Sugar Hill Gang, 1979; SR-303 c.2 (Box 18)
    - Adventures of Grandmaster Flash on the wheels of steel Performed by: Grandmaster Flash and the Furious Five, 1981; SR-321 c.2 (Box 18)
    - To the beat y'all; Loose on forty duce / Sangria Performed by: Sangria, 1981; SR-336 c.2 (Box 18)
    - I'm Sue, I'm a goodin Performed by: Sweet Carletta Sue and the Poo Poo Man Saturday Nite Band, ca. 1985; SR-367 c.2 (Box 18)
    - Summer fun Performed by: Jackie "Small" Cochran, 1980; SR-380 c.2 (Box 18)
    - Another one bites the dust Performed by: Sugar Daddy; music by Common Sense, 1980; SR-397 c.2 (Box 18)
    - TSOB Performed by: Master Jay and Michael Dee, 1980; SR-403 c.2 (Box 18)
    - Big throwdown Performed by: South Bronx, 1980; SR-405 c.2 (Box 18)
    - Virgo mechanically replayed; Let's do it Performed by: Virgo, Convertion, ca. 1980; SR-445 c.2 (Box 18)
    - Super-Wolf can do it / Super-Wolf Performed by: Super-Wolf, vocals; with instrumental acc, 1980; SR-552 c.2 (Box 18)
    - Father Goose; Father Goose II Performed by: M. Brathwaite, W. Carter, 1980; SR-616 c.2 (Box 18)
    - Father Goose; Father Goose II Performed by: M. Brathwaite, W. Carter, 1980; SR-616 c.3 (Box 18)
    - Lookin' good (shake your body) Performed by: Eddie Cheba, vocals; with instrumental ensemble, 1979; SR-617 c.2 (Box 18)
    - Son of a rapper dapper snapper / Edwin Birdsong Performed by: Edwin Birdsong, 1985; SR-772 c.2 (Box 18)
    - Pappa smerf (the big throwdown) / Electric Power Band Performed by: Electric Power Band, ca. 1985; SR-773 c.2 (Box 18)
    - Pappa smerf (the big throwdown) / Electric Power Band Performed by: Electric Power Band, ca. 1985; SR-773 c.3 (Box 18)
    - Christmas rappin' Performed by: Kurtis Blow, 1979; SR-840 c.2 (Box 18)
  - 45s and 7" records - SR 852-922, includes duplicates (Box 19)
    - Christmas in a small town; Rudy's bar and grill / Richard A Peoples Performed by: Richard A. Peoples, 1976; SR-852 (Box 19)
      Publisher: Rap Music Co.
    - Lady bug / Bumblebee Unlimited Performed by: Bumblebee Unlimited, 1978; SR-853 (Box 19)
      Publisher: F1Team
    - Do it ('til you're satisfied); Do it ('til you're satisfied) part II Performed by: B.T. Express, 1974; SR-854 (Box 19)
      Publisher: Scepter Records
    - Whip / Darnell Simpkins and the Family Tree Performed by: Darnell Simpkins and the Family Tree, ca. 1975; SR-855 (Box 19)
      Publisher: SCM
      Track listing: The whip (part I) -- The whip (part II)
    - Disco-fied; (It's time to) boogie down / Rhythm Heritage Performed by: Rhythm Heritage, 1976; SR-856 (Box 19)
      Publisher: ABC Records
    - Salsoul hustle; Salsoul / Salsoul Orchestra Performed by: the Salsoul Orchestra; Vincent Montana, 1975; SR-857 (Box 19)
    - Street talk / BCG (BC Generation) Performed by: B.C. Generation; featuring Bob Crewe, Cindy Bullens, 1976; SR-858 (Box 19)
      Publisher: 20th Century
      Track listing: Street talk -- Street talk (var. II)
    - Happiness (is so far away); Gigin / Hindal Butts Performed by: Hindal Butts, 1968; SR-859 (Box 19)
      Publisher: Kool Kat Records
      Track listing: Happiness (is so far away) (vocal) -- Gigin (instrumental)
    - Impeachment story Performed by: Various performers, 1974; SR-860 (Box 19)
      Publisher: Peach-Mint
      Track listing: "The impeachment story" (Steel, Jake and Jeff) -- "Heavy steppin'" (Lou Toby and his Heavies)
    - Feel like good music; Catch a groove / Juice Performed by: Juice, 1976; SR-861 (Box 19)
      Publisher: Greedy Records Ltd.
      Track listing: Feel like good music -- Catch a groove.
    - All day music; Summer / War Performed by: War, 1976; SR-862 (Box 19)
      Track listing: All day music -- Summer.
    - Breakdown; Pull up to the bumper / Grace Jones Performed by: Grace Jones, 1980; SR-863 (Box 19)
      Track listing: Breakdown -- Pull up to the bumper.
    - Yes sir, I can boogie; Cara mia / Baccara Performed by: Baccara, 1977; SR-864 (Box 19)
      Publisher: RCA Records
      Track listing: Yes sir, I can boogie -- Cara mia.
    - Love on delivery (LOD); One into one / The Reflections Performed by: Reflections, 1975; SR-865 (Box 19)
      Track listing: Love on delivery (L.O.D.) -- One into one.
    - TSOP (The sound of Philadelphia); Something for nothing Performed by: MFSB, Three Degrees, Thom Bell, 1973; SR-866 (Box 19)
      Publisher: Philadelphia International Records; Distributed by CBS Records
      Track listing: TSOP (MFSB, featuring the Three Degrees) -- Something for nothing (MFSB, featuring Thom Bell)
    - Bump me baby / Dooley Silverspoon Performed by: Dooley Silverspoon, 1975; SR-867 (Box 19)
      Publisher: Cotton
      Track listing: Bump me baby (pt. 1) -- Bump me baby (pt. 2)
    - Soul makossa; Lily / Manu Dibango Performed by: Manu Dibango, 1973; SR-868 (Box 19)
      Track listing: Soul makossa (the original version) -- Lily.
    - Born to lose; I wanna be around / Dora Hall Performed by: Dora Hall, ca. 1975; SR-869 (Box 19)
      Publisher: Calamo Records
    - NY, you got me dancing; Keep it up longer / Andrea True Connection Performed by: Andrea True Connection; Gregg Diamond, 1977; SR-870 (Box 19)
      Publisher: Buddah Records
    - Party / Silk Performed by: Silk, vocals; with instrumental acc, 1976; SR-871 (Box 19)
      Track listing: Party, pt. 1 -- Party, pt. 2.
    - Chinese Kung Fu / Banzaii Performed by: Banzaii, 1975; SR-872 (Box 19)
      Track listing: Chinese Kung Fu (subway) -- Chinese Kung Fu (disco version)
    - Stretch / Detroit Sex Machines Performed by: Detroit Sex Machines, 2002; SR-873 (Box 19)
      Publisher: Soul Track Production; Soul Fire Records
      Track listing: The Stretch, pt. 1 -- The Stretch, pt. 2.
    - White lines (don't don't do it) / Grandmaster and Melle Mel Performed by: Grandmaster Flash and Melle Mel, 1983; SR-874 (Box 19)
    - Que pasa; Me no pop I / Kid Creole & Coconuts present Coati Mundi Performed by: Kid Creole and the Coconuts, ca. 1980; SR-875 (Box 19)
      Track listing: Que pasa/Me no pop I -- Me no pop I.
    - Bras on 45 / Ivor Biggun Performed by: Ivor Biggun and others, ca. 1975; SR-876 (Box 19)
      Publisher: Dead Badger Records
      Track listing: Bras on 45 (family version) disco cut -- Are mice electric -- Richard the Third.
    - Shock, shock, the house / D.J. Hollywood Performed by: D.J. Hollywood, 1980; SR-877 (Box 19)
    - Beat Street breakdown Performed by: Grandmaster Flash, Melle Mel and the Furious Five, 1984; SR-878 (Box 19)
      Publisher: Atlantic Recording Corp.
      Track listing: Beat Street breakdown, pt. I -- Beat Street breakdown, pt. II.
    - Message / Grand Master Flash & the Furious Five Performed by: Grandmaster Flash, 1982; SR-879 (Box 19)
      Publisher: Disques Vogue: Sugar Hill
    - Holiday rap; Whimsical touch / MC Miker "G" & Deejay Sven Performed by: MC Miker "G" & Deejay Sven, 1986; SR-880 (Box 19)
      Publisher: Debut Records
      Track listing: Holiday rap -- Whimsical touch.
    - Super rappin' no. 2; Super rappin' theme / Grand Master Flash and the Furious Five Performed by: Grandmaster Flash, 1980; SR-881 (Box 19)
      Track listing: Super rappin' no. 2 (vocal) -- Super rappin' theme (instrumental)
    - Super rappin' no. 2; Super rappin' theme / Grand Master Flash and the Furious Five Performed by: Grandmaster Flash, 1980; SR-881 c.2 (Box 19)
    - Flying saucer Performed by: [Unknown], ca. 1980; SR-882 (Box 19)
      Publisher: Radio Active Records
      Track listing: Flying saucer, part I -- Flying saucer, part II.
    - Lady bug Performed by: Bumblebee Unlimited, 1978; SR-883 (Box 19)
      Publisher: Red Greg Records
    - Humanap ka ng panget!; Ganyan! / Andrew E Performed by: Andrew E, vocals, 1990; SR-884 (Box 19)
      Publisher: Viva Records
      Track listing: Humanap ka ng panget -- Ganyan!
    - They're coming to take me away, ha-haaa! / Napoleon XIV Performed by: Napoleon XIV, 1966; SR-885 (Box 19)
    - Gimme a break / Bobby Gilliom Performed by: Bobby Gilliom, 1983; SR-886 (Box 19)
      Track listing: Gimme a break / Bobby Gilliom -- A dub break (instrumental) / Clappa Club.
    - Get on up / Jazzy Dee Performed by: Jazzy Dee, 1983; SR-887 (Box 19)
      Track listing: Get on up -- Get on up (instrumental).
    - (Hey you) Rock Steady Crew / Rock Steady Crew Performed by: Rock Steady Crew, 1983; SR-888 (Box 19)
      Track listing: (Hey you) Rock Steady Crew -- Rock Steady Crew (instrumental version)
    - Rapp payback (Where iz Moses?) / James Brown Performed by: James Brown, 1981; SR-889 (Box 19)
      Publisher: Frog Records
      Track listing: Rapp payback pt. 1 -- Rapp payback pt. 2.
    - 1st Avenue Performed by: Various performers; composed by Robert Road and George Rap, 1984; SR-890 (Box 19)
      Publisher: Raproad
      Track listing: 1st Avenue -- 1st Avenue (instrumental version)
    - AJ is cool / Kurtis Blow Performed by: Kurtis Blow, 1985; SR-891 (Box 19)
    - Magic electronic; 5595 / Body Electric Performed by: Body Electric, 1984; SR-892 (Box 19)
      Publisher: Harlekin
    - Breaks / Kurtis Blow Performed by: Kurtis Blow, 1980; SR-893 (Box 19)
    - Rok da house Performed by: Beatmasters; featuring the Cookie Crew, 1987; SR-894 (Box 19)
      Publisher: Rhythm King Records in association with Mute Records
    - Alpenrap; I hab des G'fühl / Erste Allgemeine Verunsicherung Performed by: EAV (Erste Allgemeine Verunsicherung), 1983; SR-895 (Box 19)
      Track listing: Alpenrap -- I hab des G'fu¨hl.
    - Hollandse rep; Boerenbranding Performed by: Haagse Harry & Hollandseveldse Hendrik, 1986; SR-896 (Box 19)
      Publisher: Dureco Benelux
      Track listing: Hollandse rep -- Boerenbranding.
    - Rapfolie Performed by: Marcel Fobert and Folie Club, 1984; SR-897 (Box 19)
      Publisher: Carrere Clever
      Track listing: Rapfolie (vocal) -- Rapfolie (instrumental)
    - Napoleon XIV Performed by: Napoleon XIV, 1962; SR-898 (Box 19)
      Track listing: They're coming to take me away, ha-haaa -- Aaah-ah, yawa em ekat ot gnimoc er'yeht -- Doing the Napoleon -- I'm in love with my little red tricycle.
    - Purple mix; Purple rap / SBBL Performed by: Side A, Prince; side B, words and music by Ben Liebrand and Sander Bos (S.B.B.L.), 1985; SR-899 (Box 19)
      Track listing: Side A is a (replayed) medley of songs composed by Prince; Introduction -- 1999 -- Sex shooter -- Controversy -- I feel for you -- Erotic city -- When doves cry -- Glamorous life.
    - Scratchin' zwaantjes; Le massacre / Urbanus Performed by: Urbanus, 1984; SR-900 (Box 19)
      Publisher: Philips
      Track listing: The scratchin' zwaantjes -- Le massacre (instrumental)
    - Rap rap music; Rap attack / Graffiti Performed by: Graffiti, 1983; SR-901 (Box 19)
      Publisher: Hansa International
      Track listing: Rap rap music -- Rap attack.
    - Cut it out!; Satellite / Simon and the Piemen Performed by: Simon and the Piemen, ca. 1985; SR-902 (Box 19)
      Publisher: Chartbound
      Track listing: Cut it out! -- Satellite.
    - 8 million stories; AJ scratch / Kurtis Blow Performed by: Kurtis Blow, 1984; SR-903 (Box 19)
    - Work that sucker to death / Xavier Performed by: Xavier, 1981; SR-904 (Box 19)
    - You're my candy sweet; King Tim III (personality jock) / Fatback Performed by: Fatback, 1979; SR-905 (Box 19)
      Track listing: You're my candy sweet -- King Tim III (personality jock)
    - Spoonin rap Performed by: Spoonin Gee, 1979; SR-906 (Box 19)
      Track listing: A drive down the street -- I was spanking and freaking -- I don't drink smoke or gamble neither -- I'm the cold crushing lover.
    - Spoonin rap Performed by: Spoonin Gee, 1979; SR-906 c.2 (Box 19)
    - New York, New York Performed by: Grand Master Flash and the Furious Five, 1983; SR-907 (Box 19)
      Publisher: Sound of Scandinavia; Sugar Hill]
    - Rappers Deutsch (Rapper's delight) Performed by: G.L.S.-United (Thomas Gottschalk, Frank Laufenberg, Manfred Sexauer), 1980; SR-908 (Box 19)
      Publisher: Metronome Musik
      Track listing: Rappers Deutsch (Rapper's delight) -- Rappers Deutsch (Rapper's delight) (instrumental)
    - Rappers Deutsch (Rapper's delight) Performed by: G.L.S.-United (Thomas Gottschalk, Frank Laufenberg, Manfred Sexauer), 1980; SR-908 c.2 (Box 19)
    - Gioca-Jouer / Claudio Cecchetto Performed by: Claudio Cecchetto, ca. 1985; SR-909 (Box 19)
      Publisher: Hit Mania
    - It's good to be the king rap: part 1 & 2 / Mel Brooks, Pete Wingfield Performed by: Mel Brooks, 1981; SR-910 (Box 19)
    - Let's do it again; Cosmo rap / Ronnie Jones & Disco Circus Performed by: Ronnie Jones, 1980; SR-911 (Box 19)
    - Don't stop; Funk off Performed by: Per Cussion All Stars; featuring Grandmaster Funk, 1983; SR-912 (Box 19)
      Publisher: Silence Records
      Track listing: Don't stop (short version) -- Funk off.
    - Jail house rap; Stick 'em / Fat Boys Performed by: Fat Boys, 1984; SR-913 (Box 19)
      Publisher: Sutra: WEA
      Track listing: Jail house rap (edit.) -- Stick 'em.
    - Hip hop Performed by: [Unknown], 1984; SR-914 (Box 19)
      Publisher: CBS Disques
      Track listing: Hip hop -- Hip hop (version instrumentale)
    - Katz Rap Performed by: Ja Ja Ja, 1982; SR-915 (Box 19)
      Publisher: Ata Tak
    - Wild style theme rap / Grand Master Caz & Chris Stein Performed by: Grand Master Caz & Chris Stein, 1983; SR-916 (Box 19)
      Publisher: Chrysalis Records
      Track listing: Wild style theme rap no. 1 -- Wild style them rap no. 2.
    - Wally rap; Young and wrong / BIM Performed by: BIM, 1981; SR-917 (Box 19)
      Publisher: Swerve Records
      Track listing: Wally rap -- Young and wrong.
    - Rat rapping Performed by: Roland Rat Superstar; Steve Jeffries, 1983; SR-918 (Box 19)
      Publisher: Rodent Records
      Track listing: Rat rapping -- Rat rapping (instrumental)
    - Rapper's delight / Sugar Hill Gang Performed by: Sugar Hill Gang, 1979; SR-919 (Box 19)
      Track listing: Rapper's delight pt. 1 -- Rapper's delight pt. 2.
    - Magic life coast to coast / Mr. Magic with Cuzz Band Performed by: Mr. Magic with Cuzz Band, 2003; SR-920 (Box 19)
      Publisher: Stones Throw
      Track listing: Magic life coast to coast (vocal, edit) -- Magic life coast to coast (instrumental, edit)
    - Magic life coast to coast / Mr. Magic with Cuzz Band Performed by: Mr. Magic with Cuzz Band, 2003; SR-920 c.2 (Box 19)
    - Rapper's delight / Sugarhill Gang Performed by: Sugar Hill Gang, 1979; SR-921 (Box 19)
      Track listing: Rapper's delight (short version) -- Rapper's delight (long version)
    - Poopeloo / Gantwerp Rappers Performed by: Gantwerp Rappers, 1980; SR-922 (Box 19)
      Track listing: Poopeloo -- Poopeloo (do it yourself Mr. D.J.)
  - CDs - CD 360-398 (Box 20)
    - Ecstacy Garage all stars Performed by: Grandmaster Caz (Casanova Fly), JDL, Whipper Whip, All-Mighty Kay-Gee, Rubie-Dee, Pow-Wow, MC Globe, Grandwizard Theodore, and Touch of Class Disco (Nice and Nasty 4), 1980; CD-360 (disc 1) (Box 20)
      Publisher: Ecstacy Garage
    - Ecstacy Garage all stars Performed by: Grandmaster Caz (Casanova Fly), JDL, Whipper Whip, All-Mighty Kay-Gee, Rubie-Dee, Pow-Wow, MC Globe, Grandwizard Theodore, and Touch of Class Disco (Nice and Nasty 4), 1980; CD-361 (disc 2) (Box 20)
    - T connection Performed by: Nice & Nasty and Cold Crush, 1981; CD-362 (Box 20)
    - Treacherous Three Anniversary Performed by: Cold Crush Brothers and the Fearless 4, 1983; CD-363 (Box 20)